Guillermo Del Pino

Santiago, RM | Contact me on LinkedIn for more information. https://www.linkedin.com/in/gdelpinocastro/

I have experience as an intern at the market risk department of Santander Chile. Additionally, I have worked as a support lecturer at Adolfo Ibáñez University in subjects such as Calculus and Algebra. I'm, a proficient programmer in a few languages, specifically when it comes to implementing financial models. Additionally, I have knowledge on varied subjects of quantitative finance such as stochastic calculus, option pricing, fixed-income derivatives, exotic options, among other topics.

Work Experience

SANTANDER

Market & Capital Risk Internship – (Aug. 2023- Nov. 2023)

MARIA BOOTH

E-commerce support and Online Marketing—(Nov. 2022- Feb. 2023)

ADOLFO IBAÑEZ UNIVERSITY

Teaching Assistant: Algebra I– (2020) Teaching Assistant: Calculus I– (2020)

Teaching Assistant: Argumentative Writing—(2021)

Education

ADOLFO IBAÑEZ UNIVERSITY Master of Financial Engineering – (2023-2024)

Dynamic Asset Allocation Exotic Derivative Pricing Fixed-Income Derivatives Stochastic Calculus

ADOLFO IBAÑEZ UNIVERSITY Bachelor's

Bachelor's in economics -(2019 - 2023)

Econometrics

Microeconomics, Macroeconomics

Courses & Certifications

BLOOMBERG LP – BLOOMBERG MARKET CONCEPTS December 2023

BLOOMBERG LP – BLOOMBERG MARKET CONCEPTS June 2022

UC BERKELEY – GLOBAL LEADERSHIP & INNOVATION VIRTUAL PROGRAM January 2021

Technical Skills

Bloomberg Terminal Basic

MS Excel Intermediate

Programming Languages Matlab, R, Python, VBA

Query Languages SQL

Languages

Spanish (Native) English (Advanced)